eu5.com 2014-11-23

# Welcome to eu5.com

[](https://privacy.truste.com/privacy-seal/Europe-Business-Ltd/validation?validationId=c4a837aa-7f64-45cc-9f8e-a87bf3b66497&referer=eu5.net)**Effective February 20, 2014**

This privacy statement describes how **eu5.com** collects and uses your personal information. The privacy practices of this company have been certified by TRUSTe for compliance with our [Privacy Certification Requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/index.html). 

## Tracking On This Site »

This website uses other companies to collect data about how you use this site, such as: what pages you viewed, how long you were on a particular page, or whether you filled out a form to understand how people use the site. **learn more »**

* * *

Europe Business Ltd

Tithebarn St 

Liverpool, L2 2QP

United Kingdom

Phone: +442036089845

 **TRUSTe Dispute Resolution**  
If a TRUSTe client has violated its privacy agreement you can file a complaint with [TRUSTe Dispute Resolution »](http://www.truste.com/watchdog)

 **Effective on February 20, 2014**

This privacy statement describes how **Europe Business Ltd** collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: [ eu5.com](http://eu5.com/). It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

 **Europe Business Ltd** has been awarded TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy policy and practices have been reviewed by TRUSTe for compliance with [TRUSTe's program requirements](http://www.truste.com/privacy-program-requirements/index.html) including transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. TRUSTe's mission, as an independent third party, is to accelerate online trust among consumers and organizations globally through its leading privacy trustmark and innovative trust solutions. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at [tech@eu5.com](mailto:tech@eu5.com). If you are not satisfied with our response you can contact [TRUSTe here](http://www.truste.com/about_TRUSTe/contact_us.html).

We collect the following personal information from you:

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number

As is true of most Web sites, we automatically gather information about your computer such as your IP address, browser type, referring/exit pages, and operating system.

 **We use this information to:**

  * Send you an order confirmation
  * Send you requested product or service information
  * Send product updates or warranty information
  * Respond to customer service requests
  * Administer your account
  * Send you marketing communications
  * Improve our Web site and marketing efforts
  * Respond to your questions and concerns

 **Choice/Opt-Out**

You may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [tech@eu5.com](mailto:tech@eu5.com).

We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.

We may disclose your personal information

  * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process 
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
  * if Europe Business Ltd is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
  * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

We or a third party contracted by us may use technologies such as cookies, Web beacons, or scripts to gather information about how you and others interact with our Web site. For example, we will know how many users access a specific areas or features within our site and which links or ads they clicked on. We use this aggregated information to understand and optimize how our site is used, improve our marketing efforts, and provide content and features that are of interest to you.

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [tech@eu5.com](mailto:tech@eu5.com)

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at [tech@eu5.com](mailto:tech@eu5.com). We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

 **Correcting and Updating Your Personal Information**

To review and update your personal information to ensure it is accurate, contact us at [tech@eu5.com](mailto:tech@eu5.com).

 **Notification of Privacy Statement Changes**

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

You can contact us about this privacy statement by writing or email us at the address below:

Europe Business Ltd

Tithebarn St 

Liverpool, L2 2QP

United Kingdom

Phone: +442036089845
